copypastecash.com 2014-06-29

# Privacy Policy - CopyPasteCash

* * *

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy. We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained. This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which CopyPasteCash.com and it’s parent company: OPPORTUNEX, INC. collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the http://copypastecash.com/ website (“Site”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by OPPORTUNEX, INC. 

###  1\. Personal identification information 

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, place an order, subscribe to the newsletter, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address and other information such as city, state or country. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities. 

###  2\. Non-personal identification information 

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer, geographical information, pages visited, time spent and other technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information. 

###  3\. Web browser cookies 

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. Users may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, please note that some parts of the Site may not function properly. 

###  4\. How we use collected information 

CopyPasteCash.com and it’s parent company: OPPORTUNEX, INC. collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes: 

  1. **_To personalize user experience_** We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site. 
  2. **_To improve our Site_** We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you. 
  3. **_To improve customer service_** Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs. 
  4. **_To process transactions_** We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service. 
  5. **_To send periodic emails_** The email addresses Users provide for order processing, will only be used to send them information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. If User decides to “opt-in” to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. 

###  5\. How we protect your information 

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site. Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures. 

###  6\. Sharing your personal information 

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission. 

###  7\. Third party websites 

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies. 

###  8\. Advertising 

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

###  9\. Changes to this privacy policy 

CopyPasteCash.com and it’s parent company: OPPORTUNEX, INC. has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications. 

###  10\. Your acceptance of these terms 

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and [Terms of Use](http://copypastecash.com/terms/). If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes. 

###  11\. Contacting us 

If you have any questions about these Terms or any other agreement between you and The Company, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us through our [website](http://www.copypastecash.com/contact/) or by email: at [copypastecash@gmail.com](mailto:copypastecash@gmail.com). Any legal correspondence should be directed, in writing, and addressed to OPPORTUNEX, INC. 4260 Beard Avenue North, Minneapolis, MN 55422. 

* * *

#####  This document was last updated on July 10th, 2012
